ebates.ca 2015-05-09

# Coupons, Promo Codes and Cash Back Savings - Ebates Canada

## Privacy Policy

Ebates was founded by two former Deputy District Attorneys who take privacy and security very seriously. We at Ebates Canada know that these issues are essential to making this site a success for us and our members. Rest assured that privacy, security and integrity are first and foremost at Ebates Canada.

What data we collect and why  
Who sees your personal information  
How we keep your information secure  
Your privacy with Ebates Canada  
Your privacy with our stores and advertisers  
Our policies on email  
Cookies and how are they used  
Your choices and responsibilities  
Integrity  
Third-party verification

### What data we collect and why

Our vision is to maximize the rewards for all of Ebates Canada members and to provide as many member benefits as possible. The key way in which Ebates provides value is to share with members the commissions we receive from our affiliated stores. The information we collect (name, email address, and physical address) is used to track and send the Cash Back payments members earn.

Additionally, we may use information on the stores you visit or the offers you view on Ebates.ca to select special offers that will be relevant to you. Except at an aggregate level, however, we do not share that information with our store partners or other third parties.

Finally, Ebates Canada collects data on the devices that access or attempt to access our websites. This device data is used in conjunction with a third party security partner to identify and prevent fraudulent activity and does not include personally identifiable information.

### Who sees your personal information

Only a very limited number of Ebates Canada employees ever have access to your personal information. This information is used to track and send the Cash Back payments you earn.

We may use contractors or vendors to help us provide some of the services at our site. If we need to disclose personal information for them to provide the services, it is with the requirement that the information is kept confidential and is used only for those services. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site or to protect Ebates Canada and its members from losses. 

### How we keep your information secure

The security of your personal information is important to Ebates Canada. Ebates.ca uses a secure, encrypted connection (called an SSL connection) on all pages where you access or transmit personal information.

### Your privacy with Ebates Canada

Ebates Canada will never ask for your username, password or any other personal information in an unsolicited phone call, email or letter. Further, any contact with Ebates Canada customer service in which personal information is exchanged with a customer service representative will be used only for the purpose of satisfying your request. Any personal information you provide will not be recorded or used for any reason beyond that of the stated request.

If you choose to use our referral program to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Ebates Canada stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at customercare@ebates.ca to request that we remove this information from our database.

If we change our privacy policy, we will post a change notice to this privacy statement and other appropriate places. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it regularly. If we make changes to this policy, we will notify you, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Your privacy with our stores and advertisers

Ebates Canada does not record personal information passed from our members to affiliated stores. Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to Ebates Canada, the store, or third party affiliate program management companies for accurate tracking purposes, but his information will not be released by Ebates Canada to other parties.

Ebates Canada contains links to various other sites. Each of these sites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of Ebates Canada. If you wish to receive special offers directly from a store, neither this privacy policy nor our opt-out policy applies to those communications. Instead, please refer to the relevant store's privacy and opt-out policy.

### Our policies on email

Ebates Canada sends two types of email to members: customer service emails required to maintain the Ebates Canada program (like Cash Back credits & payment notifications); and promotional emails featuring especially good offers. You may choose not to receive promotional emails at any time from My Account or by clicking the "unsubscribe" link in an email.

Ebates Canada does not support spamming by our members and we explicitly prohibit it in our Terms & Conditions. If you would like to report an incident of spamming using our tell-a-friend capability, please contact us. We will investigate and take suitable action.

### Cookies and how are they used

Cookies are small text files that a web site can write to your computer. We may use cookies to identify you and allow you to log in once to Ebates Canada and shop without having to log in again. Cookies are also used by many of our merchants to identify you as an Ebates Canada member.

Ebates Canada requires its members to have cookies enabled in order to accumulate Cash Back rewards.

### Your choices and responsibilities

Periodically we may send you emails on new features or special offers. On every one of these emails you will be given the choice to unsubscribe from Ebates Canada's promotional mailings. Simply follow the directions in any of our emails.

It is the member's responsibility to update and maintain accurate contact information in their account. You can make changes by visiting your account page and entering corrections. Email and street addresses that are entered into a member's personal profile page are the addresses that will be used for all contact including for sending you Cash Back payments. Ebates Canada is not responsible for payments sent to an incorrect addresses provided by you.

We will post all changes to this Privacy Agreement here at our site. You are responsible for checking periodically on policy updates.

### Integrity

At Ebates Canada, we know that your word is who you are and integrity is the cornerstone of any enterprise whether public, private or personal. As such, you have our word that we will protect your privacy and safeguard your shopping at all times.

### Third-party verification

Ebates is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site Ebates.ca. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact customer service. If you do not receive acknowledgment of you inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at <http://privacy.truste.com/privacy-seal/Ebates-com-Inc-/validation?rid=590a15b2-e175-4d5f-8081-002f438136e8>. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with Ebates to resolve your concerns.

Ebates Canada, Inc.  
2345 Yonge Street, Suite 410  
Toronto, ON M4P 2E5

Ebates U.S. Headquarters  
333 Bryant Street, Suite 250  
San Francisco CA, 9410
